[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which EU member has a significant part of its territory below sea level?", "correct_answer": "The Netherlands", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Poland", "Estonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these great books was first published in 1771?", "correct_answer": "The Encyclopedia Britannica", "incorrect_answers": ["Gullivers Travels", "Roberts Rules of Order", "Paradise Lost"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Soylent Green\u2019s storyline, what were educated people called in 2022?", "correct_answer": "Books", "incorrect_answers": ["Infostations", "Furniture", "Almanacs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call a storage place for bees?", "correct_answer": "Apiary", "incorrect_answers": ["A bee zoo", "Asterciary", "Aviary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What directed the 1977 movie Close Encounters of the Third Kind?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Ridley Scott", "Alfred Hitchcock", "Robert Zemeckis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred as mercenary Danny Archer in the 2006 movie Blood Diamond?", "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Cruise", "Ben Affleck", "Jamie Foxx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ailurophobia is fear of these animals.", "correct_answer": "Cats", "incorrect_answers": ["Horses", "Dogs", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You live in Ossining, NY, USA  and you call your friend in Honolulu, Hawaii. Its the month of May. How many hours time difference are there between these 2 locales?", "correct_answer": "6 Hours Difference", "incorrect_answers": ["4 Hours Difference", "3 Hours Difference", "5 Hours Difference"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To prepare this one, you need 1 1/2 oz. Kahlua, 1/2 oz. peppermint schnapps, splash of cream and splash of cola. Shake the ingredients and add ice.", "correct_answer": "Colorado Minty Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Cosmopolitan", "Vodka Martini", "Georgia Peach"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Superbad, when Seth leaves a party, he has these filled up with beer because they are easy to carry.", "correct_answer": "Laundry Soap Containers", "incorrect_answers": ["Bleech Containers", "Bubble Bath Bottles", "Shampoo Bottles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the alien ship land at the end of the movie Close Encounters of the Third Kind?", "correct_answer": "Devils Tower, Wyoming", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Rocks, Colorado", "None of these", "Death Valley, California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Yorkshire Terriers average lifespan?", "correct_answer": "11 - 13 years", "incorrect_answers": ["5 - 8 years", "15 - 18 years", "99 - 101 years"]}]